marvin.ie 2017-11-15

# Marvin.ie Privacy Policy

Marvin.ie respects the privacy of all visitors to our website. This Privacy Statement outlines our policy concerning the collection and use of personal information which is gathered by Marvin.ie from users of this website.

We may update our Privacy Statement from time to time to reflect any changes in technology or legislation, which may affect the way in which we process your personal information. Marvin.ie is not responsible for the privacy practices of any external websites which may be accessed through your use of this website and so we would advise that you review the privacy statements of those websites as they may be subject to different privacy requirements.

Any processing of personal information gathered by Marvin.ie as a result of your use of this website is governed by the provisions of the Irish Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003. In general, its agents and service providers will only use within Marvin.ie and any information you provide to Marvin.ie.

Your information will be disclosed where we are obliged or permitted by law.  Also, if you post or send offensive, inappropriate or objectionable content anywhere on or to Marvin.ie or otherwise engage in any disruptive behaviour on Marvin.ie, Marvin.ie can use whatever information that is available to it about you to stop such behaviour.

This may involve informing relevant third parties such as your employer, school e-mail/Internet provider and law enforcement agencies about the content and your behaviour. Information cannot be used to contact employer, school or email/internet provider only the Gardai.

When you supply any personal information to Marvin.ie (e.g. for competitions) we have legal obligations towards you in the way we use those data.

We must collect the information fairly, that is, we must explain how we will use it (see the notices on particular webpages that let you know why we are requesting the information) and tell you if we want to pass the information on to anyone else (seek your consent to pass it on to third parties).

## **What personal information does Marvin.ie collect when I visit its website?**

When you enter a competition Marvin.ie may collect information about your postal or email address. If you sign up for our alerts service we may also collect similar information. If you place an online order via Marvin.ie to a Restaurant we may have details of your method of payment and your address.

The aim of this privacy policy is to explain how Marvin.ie collects and uses the personal information it gathers about you through the use of the Marvin.ie website. Marvin.ie will ensure that it keeps all personal information supplied by you in accordance with its obligations under current Data Protection legislation.

You may be asked to provide personal information, such as your mobile phone number if you wish to participate in competitions or if you wish to sign up to any of the Marvin.ie email alert services. This information is not disclosed to any third party without receiving your prior consent.

When you supply any personal information to Marvin.ie. (e.g. for competitions) we have legal obligations towards you in the way we use those data. We must collect the information fairly, that is, we must explain how we will use it (see the notices on particular webpages that let you know why we are requesting the information) and tell you if we want to pass the information on to anyone else.

In general, its agents and service providers will only use within Marvin.ie and any information you provide to Marvin.ie. Your information will be disclosed where we are obliged or permitted by law. Also, if you post or send offensive, inappropriate or objectionable content anywhere on or to Marvin.ie or otherwise engage in any disruptive behaviour on Marvin.ie, Marvin.ie can use whatever information that is available to it about you to stop such behaviour.

This may involve informing relevant third parties such as your employer, school e-mail/Internet provider and law enforcement agencies about the content and your behaviour. We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as you use the service you have requested, and remove it in the event that the purpose has been met. Where personal information is held for people who are not yet registered but have taken part in other Marvin.ie.com services (e.g. competitions), that information will be held as long as is necessary to ensure that the service is run smoothly. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely, in accordance with the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003.

The period of retention is outlined in the Terms and Conditions of competitions and services. If you are notified on Marvin.ie that your information may be used to allow Marvin.ie to contact you for “service administration purposes”, this means that Marvin.ie may contact you for a number of purposes related to the service you have signed up for.

For example, we may wish to provide you with password reminders or notify you that the particular service has been suspended for maintenance. We will not contact you for promotional purposes, such as notifying you of improvements to the service or new services Marvin.ie.com unless you specifically agree to be contacted for such purposes at the time you submit your information on the site, or at a later time if you sign up specifically to receive such promotional information.

Marvin.ie.com uses cookies. Cookies are small text files sent from a website and stored in the user’s web browser while user is browsing a website. When users visit the same website again, the browser sends cookies back to the website allowing the website to recognise the user and remember things like personalised details or preferences. Marvin.ie’s policy concerning the use of cookies on Marvin.ie is outlined in our Cookie Policy. This information is then used by us to monitor access to our site and to develop and improve the service we provide to our customers accordingly. The Marvin.ie site contains links with third party sites.

This privacy statement does not apply to these sites and Marvin.ie is not responsible for the privacy practice or the contents of these third party websites.

If you are aged 18 or under please ask your parent or guardian for their permission to provide us with your contact information. If you have any questions or queries about this policy statement please contact our helpdesk.

## How do I know my personal information is kept safe and secure if I choose to provide my details for services on the site?

Marvin.ie servers which hold any personal information are on site off our third-party hosting campus in secure locations. Credit and debit card details are stored in an encrypted form for additional security.

## How will Marvin.ie use my information?

If as a result of any communications with Marvin.ie through the website Marvin.ie acquires any personal information about its visitors Marvin.ie guarantees that the information will only be used for the purposes for which it is gathered and will not be distributed or used for any other purpose.

## Do you pass any personal information to third parties?

It is not Marvin.ie policy to pass on personal information to any third parties.

## Do you transfer any of the information collected abroad for other purposes?

Marvin.ie does not transfer any personal information abroad

## Is the website hosted within the European Union?

Yes, the Marvin.ie website is hosted within the European Union.

## How long will my information be retained by Marvin.ie?

Marvin.ie also guarantees that personal information will not be retained for longer than it is required and that once the initial purposes for gathering the information have become irrelevant the information will not be retained.

## How can I request a copy of my personal information held by Marvin.ie collected through using this website?

Any individual has a right to make an access request, in writing, under Section 4 of the Data Protection Acts for a copy of their personal data held by Marvin.ie.

Marvin.ie may ask for further identification information before the information is released and may charge a maximum fee of €6.35 for the supply of this information to you.

Marvin.ie has 40 days to comply with the access request, subject to the provisions of the Data Protection Acts. It should be noted that under section 21 of the Data Protection (Amendment) Act 2003 there are specific exemptions relating to personal information held for journalistic, artistic and literary purposes.

If members of the public wish to see what personal information Marvin.ie may hold on them, please contact our helpdesk or write to:

Data Protection

Marvin Food Online Limited

7 Apollo Business Park

Dundrum Road

Dundrum

Dublin 14

General information on Data Protection is available from the Office of the Data Protection Commissioner’s [website](http://www.dataprotection.ie/).

© Copyright 2017 Marvin Food Online Ltd • 2nd Floor Skylab Building, 2 Exchange Street Upper, Dublin 8, D08 XW7D • Co Reg: 557072 • [info@marvin.ie](mailto:info@marvin.ie).
